come in come in
hi my name is
to meet you Mr Khan I'm Stephanie
mathura oh why are you here today sir
well before we begin let me ask you a
few questions would you like anything to
drink level coffee let me just get you
one right now okay
there you go I need some Starbucks
thanks a lot
sure my secretary makes it so I don't
know okay tell your secretary I said
thanks I have a uh how's the weather
outside it's still snowing outside or
it's it's a little chilly here and there
but you know it's Canada yeah it's I
don't understand Canada anymore man it's
snowing in Spring like come on
that's why I love it
well
Stefan you look really familiar to me
haven't met you before
my
I don't know
are you sure what kind of policy did you
go to did you go to I went to Sheridan
College for a couple years but then for
business
then I kind of went into Dentistry but
wait sharing colleague just sharing
College that's where I got it that's
where I got my diploma as well from did
you go to finance yeah from I believe it
was 2011 until 2013. no way you guys I
wouldn't last the same year wait were
you were you my primary for selling
Financial Services
remember that Professor we had John
something John
Dobby yeah everywhere now yeah oh my
gosh so you were my whole world isn't it
yeah
like remember how we had to do that last
presentation about how to sell a
financial service but I guess I didn't
help you out because you're at the
Dentistry I'm doing what I learned
that's good that's good
thank you
so why do you change fields
I really wanted to make my my father
that because he just recently passed and
he just left me with a whole lot of
depth to pay back so I just wanted to
make him happy and you know you know
make them make them feel like he has
that one good son
you understand what I'm saying yeah
that's totally I totally understand what
he's saying I'm sad to hear that your
dad passed away but it's a good thing he
came here today
so to talk about I'm guessing life
insurance if you're because
so can we start do you mind if you start
talking business that's okay with you
sure let's start
so let's just begin since I already know
that you want to get life insurance why
do you who do you want to protect with
your life insurance policies I was
looking just to protect me my wife and
my kids
for the future
okay do you have any wait you have kids
yeah I've got two actually get a picture
of it or that I mean
actually do
come check them out
right here so right here oh my God
you're so cute this is the this is the
three-year-old and this is the
two-year-old and that's what my wife
looks like huh
upgrades I see good job times have
changed buddy I know
so let's get to business you said life
insurance that's funny because life
insurance nowadays is a commodity a lot
of people don't know that I just sold 10
life insurance policies like this week
itself really we could I could clearly
see that you're really liking your job
but
I didn't think that life insurance was a
commodity nowadays I guess times have
changed since uh we lost since we were
kids
but like I was saying before the main my
main priority of getting life insurance
is
so I could protect my family
that's a good thing you came to manual
today we provided one of the best the
financial products and Wealthy
communication accumulation
products backfire Financial strength and
security and of our security of our
global leaders such as myself
you know me since College I've always
been a hard worker even during that
project we had
I'll always waiting for money I had two
jobs
and now I'm here and now it's been for
my hard work has been paying off I have
a portfolio worth of one million dollars
yeah and I like to add you on to it so
I'm gonna ask you a few questions
yeah that's fine you're the professional
here so I'm going to take a few notes
without my laptop okay anyway so I'm
gonna start with
um how many family members do you want
to cover all myself yeah wife my two
kids
but I want separate accounts for all of
them and today I'm just I just want you
to I just want to talk to you so I can
get a simple understanding of what what
I'm here for on the types of assurances
that you offer
okay well let's start with the basics so
you know about them the first is term
term life insurance is basically if you
it's uh you pick a specific time or
years or you say like I'm I believe I'm
gonna die in 10 years and you pick that
and you pay the premium for that the
second one is the whole life insurance
so it's basically your whole lifetime
but it goes all your premiums the whole
into a savings account so your
traditional savings account one percent
two percent okay and the last one is
universal life insurance which I think
is the best one to pick because
um you could contribute as much as you
want could that count do it and the more
you contribute you can basically
and that's more and and there's 50
different mutual funds they can invest
in within that account it's a faster way
to grow your money and in the end you'll
have a bigger amount of money which is
tax free that's the best thing about it
so your family will have no no issues
okay really interested in the universal
life machines because you know how I
have that little Finance background from
from the Sheridan case yeah I remember
so I know the ins and outs of how to
invest but of course you're a
professional here I'm putting all my
trust into you
hopefully we can make something happen
no worries man I just got to ask you
these two questions then we can figure
out what works out for you okay so do
you make maximum your do you make an
actual contribution to your traditional
accounts such as your rrsp tax free
savings account
yes next one is do you do you want to
leave a tax
um tax-free benefit for your loved ones
um
yes
I don't want my money taxable
uh I just want my family to have a full
amount would that be uh would that be
doable sense why is Andrew since you
make the maximum contribution to your
IRS freeze and your tax free savings
account and you also want uh tax-free
benefit for your family
pass on knock on wood
this program that I put your answers in
suggested that we put your that we
choose Ultra Vision for you
so all tradition is basically you get
your brochure right here
is there a brochure about ultravision
but I'll tell you about it so it's
basically a unique way to simplify and
invest your life insurance
uh it has a tax advantage growth within
the policy and is able to accumulate
wealth and accumulate wealth and
beneficiary tax
so your beneficiaries the tax-free
amount
and the unique features are within the
page right here it basically just states
that
um you could put in as much as you want
um and you can invest it any way you
want
oh I see
so it's basically when you're gonna go
home tonight just take the brochure and
you can Flinch your wife what author
vision is and why you got it okay sounds
good sounds good so if you have any
questions about
ultravision or anything else
I actually have one question
you know how we know each other right
yeah because they get a little discount
you know table stuff I wish I could do
that but I would lose my job it's
actually they have a compliance officer
now so I can't really do that but what
do you think about the policy itself the
Ultra Vision
I think the policy is good for me but in
all fairness I just have to talk to my
wife
about this because I don't usually make
the big financial decisions between the
both of us he's usually the one that
makes
makes everything clear because if I I
usually sign up for everything I see
so if she's the one who you know kind of
balances everything out and also this is
a huge amount to invest every month
so if you don't mind I like to
talk about it talk talk it over with my
life
definitely understand where you're
coming from about how you want to talk
to your wife and you think this is a
huge amount but let's let's answer your
first question or your first objection
um
yeah I know you understand the markets
yeah how fluctuates up and down and many
customers have made a similar comment
like you they have all said I'll come
back I'll wait a day
and once they got home and he told your
wife or they waited a week
the Market's changed the rates change so
we couldn't they basically it could have
gone up and they would have lost money
so I'm telling you if you get it today
you're basically guaranteed a growth
that'll go up because it is a safe
mutual fund that you're going to get
invest in I totally forgot and I want
you to make a lot of money
with me so okay sounds good but I
totally forgot how the market reacts and
um are there any monthly premiums I
should worry about
monthly premiums oh like I showed you
the math before well we just did so
basically you're spending 683 for four
members that's a pretty good idea and
your child your children are only two
and three so by 10 or 20 maybe probably
listen to the amount 50 yeah and
it should be fine but if something
happens to you you're killing her
perfectly fine and no deaths you'll your
debts will be paid off
right because uh actually sounds decent
oh since I show you the math already
and it's only 683 for four members to
put on the policy your children only two
and three so buy 10 or 20 or if
something happens to you in the Midway
the amount you're gonna put in 683 per
month that's gonna be amazing for them
and then you'll basically pay off your
house loan your car whatever you need
right yeah
but they think of it that way to be
honest but it actually sounds like
you're giving me a solid deal
yeah just um it sounds so good that you
know what I'm gonna sign them all right
do you have the papers for me to sign or
whatever yeah what do you think funny
thing I don't have a paper see you gotta
go to my secretary okay go over here
tell her I sent you yeah of course and
then come back with the paper sign and
then I can start your investment account
with you right away and then you can
start making money while you start
saving to make money yeah I don't know
before I go you think I could grab a
business card yeah let me see if I can
find one over here oh
I leave them everywhere on the table you
know
thanks a lot boss all right thanks for
coming Stephen I'll see you in like
papers take around 30 minutes sign so
see around that time take care all right
take care brochure take your brochure
make sure you tell your wife what you
just did okay
take care boss